rcgp.org.uk 2012-05-19

# Royal College of General Practitioners - Privacy Policy

* * *

The Royal College of General Practitioners website does not collect or store personal information about individuals, except where you choose to give us information, either  via online ordering, the membership application process, or in online forms or emails you may send to the College. On the website, membership application data or that gathered by forms or emails is used solely for the purpose of the members’ login.

The website uses cookies only if you select the "remember me" option when logging in to the members’ area, or ordering from the online bookstore. The sole purpose of this is convenience, making it unnecessary to retype your username and password every time you logon.

The [Online Bookstore](http://www.rcgp.org.uk/bookshop/Terms_and_Conditions.html) pages provide further information about processing of data collected via online ordering.

All personal data is processed in accordance with the  Data Protection Act 1998. We will not pass any of your personal data to outside organisations or individuals without your express consent.

You have a right to know about the personal information the RCGP holds about you, and to have your data corrected or deleted . Our [Data Protection Policy](http://www.rcgp.org.uk/systempages/data_protection_policy.aspx "Data Protection policty") is available on the website. Please address requests or queries about our data protection policies to the [Data Protection Officer](mailto:meastwell@rcgp.org.uk "Email the Data Protection Officer") at this address.

For information on how to disable cookies read the “[How to disable cookies](http://www.rcgp.org.uk/systempages/privacy_policy/disabling_cookies.aspx "How to disable cookies")” page.

**Version 1.1,  3 February 2006**
